codeavengers.com 2014-07-04

# Code Avengers, privacy policy

Your privacy is important to Online Education Limited (referred to in this Privacy Policy as we, our or us). This Privacy Policy governs our collection, use and disclosure of your personal information and has been prepared in accordance with our obligations and your rights set out in the Privacy Act 1993. We may modify or amend this Privacy Policy at any time and for any reason. By using our website you consent to our use of your personal information in accordance with this Privacy Policy (as amended by us from time to time). 

This Privacy Policy explains: 

  * what kind of personal information we collect; 
  * where we collect personal information from; 
  * how we use personal information; 
  * how we store personal information; 
  * how you can access/amend your personal information; 
  * how long we hold personal information; and 
  * who you can contact for further information. 

  1. What kind of personal information we collect 

We only collect the personal information you give to us. This may include your name, address, email address, contact telephone number and IP address. We may also keep a record of any information that you acquire from us. 

  2. Where we collect personal information from 

We collect personal information about you by the following means: 

    * when you contact us enquiring about the products and services we provide; 
    * when we provide information, products or services to you; and 
    * indirectly when you use our website, including by storing cookies. 
  3. How we use personal information 

We may use your personal information for the following purposes: 

    * to reply to your queries; 
    * to provide you with information, products or services; 
    * to promote our products and services; 
    * to comply with relevant laws and regulations; 
    * to assess your credit-worthiness and enforce our payment rights; 
    * for any specific purpose which we notify you of at the time your personal information is collected; and 
    * for our administrative purposes. 

We may disclose information about you (including your identity): 

    * to a third party if we are required to do so by law, or in the course of legal proceedings, prospective legal proceedings or other investigations; 
    * to our service providers to the extent required to provide our information, products and services to you; or 
    * if we determine that the disclosure is necessary in connection with a complaint regarding your use of our information, products and services or our website. 

Where we disclose your personal information to our agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, we ensure that the agent or sub-contractor in question is required to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

In the event that we or our website is sold or otherwise transferred to another party, we reserve the right, to the extent permitted by law, to transfer your personal (and non-personal) information to the relevant transferee. 

  4. How we store personal information 

We store personal information electronically and in paper based form. The personal information is kept safe and secure using generally accepted standards of security. 

We may store information about you using cookies (files which are sent by us to your computer or other access device) which we can access when you visit our website. We do this to understand how our customers use our website and for administration of the website. 

  5. How you can access/amend your personal information 

You may access your personal information that we hold by emailing us at [insert contact details]. We will provide you with a copy of the personal information we keep about you. 

You may request that the personal information we hold about you be corrected by emailing us at [insert contact details]. If we agree that your personal information is to be corrected we will provide you with an amended record of your personal information. 

  6. How long we hold personal information 

We will keep your personal information for only as long as necessary for use in connection with the purpose for which it was collected. 

  7. Personal Information of Children 

Where we collect personal information from a person under 13 (Child) we will not require the Child to disclose any more personal information than is necessary for that Child to participate in any activity on our website. 

Where you are a parent of a Child you may: 

    * review your Child’s personal information that we hold by emailing us at [insert contact details]; 
    * direct us to delete any personal information about your Child that we hold; 
    * notify us that you do not consent to us collecting or using any further personal information about your Child, or disclosing such personal information to a third party. 

We will cease collection, use and disclosure (as applicable) of your Child’s personal information that we hold in accordance with your instructions. 

  8. Who you can contact for further information 

If you have any queries about this Privacy Policy or any personal information we have collected please contact: 

Privacy Contact Person: Michael Walmsley 

Email address: mike@codeavengers.com
